

KHALEEL AHMED





PROFILE

Project lead in the selection, implementation, and lead of SAP modules & other ERP's. This role uses consulting skills, business knowledge with analysis, and SAP solution expertise to effectively integrate ERP technology into the client's business environment to achieve the client expected business results.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+971 52 856 9110 +91 96774 74157

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/khaleel-ahmed-j-9h3183146

EMAIL:

officejka@gmail.com

SKYPE:

j.khaleelahmed

KEY SKILLS

SAP Business One 10.0 HANA ERP IT/ERP AUDIT PROJECT MANAGENT(PMP) Crystal Reports Power BI HANA SQL Server MS Office

CERTIFICATIONS

SAP Business One 9.3 PMP(3Fold) ITIL V3 MCSA

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

- Over **10 years** of experience in Sr. SAP Business One HANA Functional Consultant | ERP Business Analyst & Consultant | Project Lead & Management
- Handled nearly 15+ ERP Projects using SAP Business One and other ERP's.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Project Lead - Industrial Application Software, Dubai, UAE. www.canias40.com
2021 - Present

Responsible for ERP project planning and management from inception to completion. Coordination with team and processes to complete projects on time, within budget, and with desired outcomes that are aligned with objectives.

Sr. SAP Business One HANA Functional Analyst - IT/ERP Manager Falcon Refrigerators & Oven Manufacturing, Dubai, UAE.

www.falconkitchen.com
2019 - 2021

Responsible for the implementation and support of IT/ERP – SAP Business One modules to enhance the clients' business functionality and overall performance, while maintaining a high degree of satisfaction.

Sr. SAP Business One Functional Consultant Euphoros Limited, India. www.euphoros.com 2012-2019

Analyse the business processes and scenarios of the client and recommend/develop solutions to meet the client's needs. Responsible primarily for successful implementation of SAP, providing functional expertise, guidance, presentation, and instruction on SAP products to clients.

EDUCATION

Anna University, India. April 2012 Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology

PROJECTS HANDELED SECTORS

- Manufacturing
- Trading
- Clinics & Hospitals
- Universities
- Pharma
- Construction
- Hotels
- Restaurants

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES

- Coordinate internal resources and third parties/vendors for the flawless execution of multiple projects
- Ensure that all projects are delivered on-time, within scope and within budget
- Assist in the definition of project scope and objectives, involving all relevant internal stakeholders and ensuring technical feasibility
- Ensure resource availability and allocation
- Develop a detailed project plan to monitor and track progress
- Manage changes to the project scope, project schedule, and project costs using appropriate verification techniques
- Measure performance using appropriate project management tools and techniques
- Report and escalate to management as needed
- Manage the relationship with the client and relevant stakeholders
- Perform risk management to minimize potential risks
- Establish and maintain relationships with third parties/vendors
- Create and maintain comprehensive project documentation
- Meet with clients to take detailed ordering briefs and clarify specific requirements of each project
- Delegate project tasks based on junior staff members' individual strengths, skill sets, and experience levels
- Track project performance, specifically to analyze the successful completion of short and long-term goals
 Meet budgetary objectives and make adjustments to project constraints based on financial analysis
- Develop comprehensive project plans to be shared with clients as well as other staff members
- Use and continually develop leadership skills
- Attend conferences and training as required to maintain proficiency
- Perform other related duties as assigned
- Develop spreadsheets, diagrams and road maps to document needs.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth: January 20, 1991

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married Nationality: Indian

Visa Status: Employment Visa

Linguistic Skills: English, Tamil, Hindi, Urdu, and Malayalam

Passport Number: T0892161 Father's Name: Mr. N. Jameel Ahmed Present Address: Al Rashidiya, Dubai, UAE.

DECLARATION

I hereby declared the above-given information is true to the best of my knowledge and Belief.

Yours Truly Khaleel Ahmed